

Mr Qureshi

Graduate Learning Support Assistant



Profile:

Hardworking and ambitious graduate with experience in a variety of SEN roles. My work history has taught me a combination of different skills and enabled me to work successfully under pressure in a group or as an individual. I am a caring, inspirational and dedicated Learning Support Assistant with an excellent track-record of supporting and encouraging young people to achieve their true potential. Besides having worked with children who had a variety of learning needs, I have also been involved with numerous projects, group works and presentations from which I have gained valuable, transferable skills such as communications, time-management and prioritising workload.

Skills

- Excellent customer service & care skills
- · High standard of organisational skills and techniques
- · Leadership skills and team player able to motivate others
- · Computer literate in a range of IT packages
- Able to decide what steps are needed to achieve particular goals then implement these
- · Excellent selling skills Able to spot an opportunity
- · Ability to allocate time in specific targets
- Work confidently with a group



Tel: 0208 4329844

Employment History

SEN Teaching Assistant
Chesterfield Primary School, (BumbleBee Education Agency Staff)
Jan 2016 – July 2016

- · Promote school policies on pupil behaviour.
- · Support implementation of strategies to manage behaviour.
- Providing guidance, educational and emotional support to students with learning or behavioural difficulties and special needs.
- Providing 1-1 and small group tuition to SEN students.
- Employ strategies for behaviour management and report any problems to the teacher.
- Report any progress towards targets for children with Behaviour Support Plans.
- · Provide level of attention appropriate to pupil's needs, modifying approach to ensure that desired outcomes are achieved.

Frenford Young Peoples Club, SEN Head Coach April 2013 – Present

- · Specialised sports sessions and projects teaching special needs children under 18
- · Helping children who suffer with autism, physical disabilities and behavioural issues to engage with fun activities.
- · Planning tailored activities for each student to match their abilities.
- · Coaching basketball students between ages 8-16
- · Also coach different variety of sports i.e. badminton, football, cricket
- · Captain of the Frenford Boys' SEN basketball team
- · Help pupils to develop their self-confidence, independence and abilities
- · Organise outings, social activities and sporting events

Education

Tel: 0208 4329844

London South Bank University (Sept 2010 – Sept 2013) Business Administration (BA Hon) Received Honours 2:1

MA in Real Estate (Sept 2014 – 2016)

www.bumblebee-education.co.uk